ILGWU International Relations Department Records 5780/062
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Thailand, Katie Quan, April 23-May 10, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- National Labor Committee, Haiti, Edgar Romney and Muzaffar Chishti, March, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Organizing Seminar, Guatemala, March 8-9, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Kimiyo Takagi's trip to U.S., Spring, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- ILGWU/ACTWU/FILTA/FILTEA/UILTA Conference, New York, December 1992, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Elias Banda's trip to U.S., December 2-18, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- TEKSIF Convention, Turkey, Nick Bonnano, November, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Romania, Harris Zinn, September, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Connie September's visit to U.S., June, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Mission to South Africa, Edgar Romney and Bill Lee, May, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Mission to Philippines/Thailand, Michelle Briones, March, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Mission to Philippines/Thailand, Michelle Briones, March, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Sindetex Convention, Portugal, November 8-10, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Swaziland, ITGLWF Seminar, Laurie Kellogg, September, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- ICTFU/ORIT Economic meeting, Costa Rica, October 31-November 2, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Guatemala Mission, September 15-18, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- SACTWU conference, James Parrott, April, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- ICFTU Women Conference, Ottawa, Canada, April, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- ITGLWF Seminar, South Africa, November, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- ITGLWF Women Seminar Dakar, Senegal, Judith Wineman, November, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- FITITVC Women Seminar, Caracas, Venezuela, September, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Hong Kong, Taiwan, Thailand, Joe Danahy, May, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- German and Textile Garment Congress, Wurzburg, Germany, November 5-9, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- TEKSIF Women's Symposium, Turkey, November, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Mission trips to Israel, Jewish Labor Committee, 1990-1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Mission trips to Israel, Jewish Labor Committee, 1990-1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Nicaragua elections, February, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- FTZ Seminar, Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic, April, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- ITGLWF Seminar, Lesotho, Jeff Stansbury, September 5-11, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- ILO Third Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry, Geneva, December, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- ILO Third Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry, Geneva, December, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- ICFTU/ORIT Women Seminar, Panama, January 18-22, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- ICFTU/ORIT Women Seminar, Panama, January 18-22, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Jamaica Seminar (discontinued), 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Jamaica Seminar (discontinued), 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Visitors, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Visitors, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Visitors, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Visitors, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Visitors, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Visitors, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Visitors, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Visitors, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Visitors, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Visitors, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Visitors, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO/IAD Subcommittee on International Organizing and Solidarity, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO/IAD Subcommittee on International Organizing and Solidarity, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO/IAD policies, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO/IAD policies, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO/IAD policies, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO European Office (Paris), 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO, correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Asian-American Free Labor Institute, 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- African-American Labor Center, 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- African-American Labor Center, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- AALC union-to-union programs, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- AALC union-to-union programs, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- AALC union-to-union programs, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- AALC union-to-union programs, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- AALC union-to-union programs, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- AALC union-to-union programs, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Free Trade Union Institute, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Italian Union, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- TWARO, general correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- TWARO union-to-union programs, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- SACTWU, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- SACTWU/ACTWU/ILGWU/AALC meeting, New York, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- National Conference of SACTWU, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- GEB, miscellaneous reports of other departments, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Kaiser Foundation Conference on South Africa, Washington, D.C., 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- South African ITGLWF affiliates documents, 1985-1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- ICFTU Telex News on South Africa, 1989-1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- ICFTU Telex News on South Africa, 1989-1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Union-to-union programs, 1988-1994 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Union-to-union programs, 1988-1994 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Union-to-union programs, South Africa, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Union-to-union programs, South Africa, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- U.S. AFL-CIO Policy in South Africa, 1987-1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- South Africa, general, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- South Africa, general, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- South Africa, general, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- South Africa, general, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- South Africa, general, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- South Africa, general, 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- South Africa, general, 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- South Africa, general, 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- ILO Funding for Dominican Republic Organizing Project, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Dominican Republic Organizing Project, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Honduras Organizing Project, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Honduras Organizing Project, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Honduras Organizing Project, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Follow-up to FTZ organizing seminar, Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Follow-up to FTZ organizing seminar, Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Organizing seminar, Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Organizing seminar, Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Organizing seminar, Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- FITTVC/ORI, Congress, Santiago, Chile, September, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- FITTVC/ORI, Congress, Santiago, Chile, September, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- FITTVC/ORI, Congress, Santiago, Chile, September, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- FITTVC/ORI, Congress, Mexico, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- FITTVC/ORI, Congress, Mexico, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- FITTVC/ORI, Economic Summit, Caracas, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- FITTVC/ORI, Economic Summit, Caracas, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- FITTVC/ORI, Economic Summit, Caracas, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- FITTVCC Constitution, Executive Committee members, 1976-1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- FITTVCC Constitution, Executive Committee members, 1976-1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- FITTVCC Constitution, Executive Committee members, 1976-1995 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee meeting, Buenos Aires, April, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee meeting, Buenos Aires, April, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee meeting, San Juan, Puerto Rico, May, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee meeting, San Juan, Puerto Rico, May, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee meeting, San Juan, Puerto Rico, May, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee meeting, Maracay, Venezuela, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee meeting, Maracay, Venezuela, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee meeting, Maracay, Venezuela, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee, Quioto, Ecuador, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee, Quioto, Ecuador, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee, Quioto, Ecuador, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee, Buenos Aires, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee, Buenos Aires, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Committee, Caracas, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- FITTVCC Women Committee, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- FITTVCC Women Committee, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- FITTVCC/ORI Women Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- FITTVCC/ORI Women Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- FITTVCC/ORI Meeting with Jose Ramirez, ILGWU/ACTWU, January 25, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- FITTVCC/ORI Jose Ramirez's visit to the U.S., February, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- FITTVCC correspondence, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- FITTVCC correspondence, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- FITTVCC correspondence, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- FITTVCC correspondence, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- FITTVCC correspondence, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- FITTVCC correspondence, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- ICFTU, 1982-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- ICFTU, 1982-1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- ICFTU circulars, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- ICFTU circulars, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- ICFTU circulars, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- ICFTU circulars, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- ICFTU circulars, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- ICFTU circulars (July-December), 1991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- ICFTU circulars (January-June), 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- ICFTU circulars, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- ICFTU circulars, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- ICFTU circulars, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- ICFTU Telex News, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- ICFTU Telex News, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- ICFTU Telex News, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- ICFTU Telex News, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- ICFTU Telex News, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- ICFTU Telex News, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- ITGLWF Constitution, 1972-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- ITGLWF Constitution, 1972-1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- ITGLWF officers and membership, 1978-1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- ITGLWF officers and membership, 1978-1995 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 28-29 April, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 28-29 April, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- ITGLWF Presidium, Brussels, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting,Caracas,27-28 October, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting, Caracas, 28-30 October, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting, Caracas, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 27-28 April, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- ITGLWF Presidium, Brussels, April, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting, Prague, 27-29 October, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting, Prague, October, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting, Prague, October, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 14-15 April, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 14-15 April, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 1-2 September, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Espinho, Portugal, 23-24 October, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting, Espinito, Portugal, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  25 October
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  13-14 April
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  14-15 April
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Capetown, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  November, 1 of 2
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Capetown, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  8-9 November; 2 of 2
- ITGLWF Presidium and Executive Committee Meeting, South Africa, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  November; 1 of 2
- ITGLWF Presidium and Executive Committee Meeting, South Africa, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  November; 2 of 2
- ITGLWF Presidium and Executive Committee Meeting, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting, Capetown, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  10-13 November
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  26-27 April
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Brussels, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  April
- ITGLWF Presidium and Executive Committee Meeting, Taiwan, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- ITGLWF Presidium and Executive Committee Meeting, Taiwan, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  November; 2 of 2; photo
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, Taipei, Taiwan, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  7 November
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting, Taipei, Taiwan, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  8-11 November
- ITGLWF Strategic Approaches Subcommittee, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  1 of 2
- ITGLWF Strategic Approaches Subcommittee, 1994=1995 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  2 of 2
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  May
- ITGLWF 6th World Congress, Portugal, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  October; 1 of 3
- ITGLWF 6th World Congress, Portugal, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  October; 2 of 3
- ITGLWF 6th World Congress, Portugal, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  October; 3 of 3
- ITGLWF 6th World Congress, Espinito, Portugal, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  28-29 October
- ITGLWF Health and Safety, 1989-1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- ITGLWF Health and Safety, 1989-1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- ITGLWF Health and Safety, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- ITGLWF Health and Safety, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- ITGLWF General Correspondence, 1994-1994 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- ITGLWF General Correspondence, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- ITGLWF General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- ITGLWF General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- ITGLWF General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- ITGLWF Letters to All Affiliates, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- ITGLWF Letters to All Affiliates, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- ITGLWF Letters to All Affiliates, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- ITGLWF Letters to All Affiliates, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- ITGLWF Letters to All Affiliates, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- ITGLWF Affiliation Fees, 1977-1996 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- ITGLWF Affiliation Fees, 1977-1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- ITGLWF European Trade Union Committee, 1981-1995 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- ITGLWF News, Africa, 1978-1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- ITGLWF News, Africa, 1978-1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- ITGLWF News, Asia, 1982-1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- ITGLWF News, Asia, 1982-1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- ITGLWF News, Europe, 1980-1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- ITGLWF News, Europe, 1980-1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- ITGLWF News, Latin America, 1986-1995 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 8th Joint Conference, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  1 of 5
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 8th Joint Conference, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  2 of 5
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 8th Joint Conference, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  3 of 5
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 8th Joint Conference, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  4 of 5
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 8th Joint Conference, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  5 of 5
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 7th Joint Conference, Tokyo, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  March; 1 of 2; photo
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 7th Joint Conference, Tokyo, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  March; 2 of 2
- ILGWU/ACTWU/Zensen 7th Joint Conference, Tokyo, correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  1 of 3
- ILGWU/ACTWU/Zensen 7th Joint Conference, Tokyo, correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  2 of 3
- ILGWU/ACTWU/Zensen 7th Joint Conference, Tokyo, correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  3 of 3
- ILGWU/ACTWU/Zensen 7th Joint Conference, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 6th Joint Conference, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 6th Joint Conference, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 6th Joint Conference, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 6th Joint Conference, Joint Statement, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Zensen 6th Joint Conference Photographs, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 5th Joint Conference, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 5th Joint Conference, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 5th Joint Conference, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Zensen/ILGWU/ACTWU 5th Joint Conference, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Zensen Correspondence, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Zensen Correspondence, 1985-1994 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Japan Institute of Labour, David Melman, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Japan Institute of Labor, 1984-1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Japan Institute of Labour, 1984-1990 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Workshop on International Solidarity, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Zensen, James Parrott, Certificate of Honorary Lecturer, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Zensen Japanese Labor, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Japan Institute of Labor, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Zensen, 1986-1992 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Zensen, 1986-1992 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Zensen Delegation, 1978-1990 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Regional: Africa, 1980-1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Regional: Africa, 1980-1994 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Regional: Asia, 1983-1994 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Regional: Caribbean, 1979-1995 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Regional: Caribbean, 1979-1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Regional: Latin America, 1978-1991 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Regional: Eastern Europe, 1988-1995 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Regional: Europe, 1983-1993 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Regional: Europe, 1983-1993 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Regional: Central America, 1982-1993 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Regional: Pacific, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Regional: Middle East, 1990-1994 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Regional: Middle East, 1990-1994 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Clippings, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Clippings, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Clippings, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Clippings, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Clippings, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Afghanistan, 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Algeria, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Angola, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Albania, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Argentina, 1978-1994 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Argentina, 1978-1994 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Australia, 1982-1994 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Austria, 1981-1995 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Bangladesh, 1990-1995 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Barbados, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Basque Province, 1979-1981 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Belgium, 1990-1994 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Bolivia, 1978-1993 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Brazil, 1980-1995 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Brazil, 1980-1995 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Burma (Myanmar), 1992-1995 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Bulgaria, 1990-1995 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Bulgaria (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Bulgaria, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  1 of 4
- Bulgaria, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  2 of 4
- Bulgaria, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  3 of 4
- Bulgaria, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  4 of 4
- Cambodia, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Canada, 1980-1995 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Canada, 1980-1995 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Canada, 1980-1995 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Central and Eastern Europe, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Chile, 1978-1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Chile, 1978-1995 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Chile, 1978-1995 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- China (Box 31, Folder 4)
- China (Box 31, Folder 5)
- China Press Clips, General, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- China Press Clips, General, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- China Press Clips, General, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- China Press Clips, General, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- China, Trade/Economy, and Human Rights, 1992-1995 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- China, Forced Prison Labor, 1990-1994 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- China, Dissidents, 1990-1994 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- China, Dissidents, 1990-1994 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- China, Dissidents, 1990-1994 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- China, Documents (reports, statements, speeches, resolutions, press releases), 1990-1995 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- China, Documents (reports, statements, speeches, resolutions, press releases), 1990-1995 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- China, Documents (reports, statements, speeches, resolutions, press releases), 1990-1995 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Colombia, 1978-1995 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Costa Rica, 1986-1995 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Cote D'Ivoire, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Cuba, 1981-1995 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Cuba, 1981-1995 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Cuba, 1981-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Cuba: AFL-CIO Committee for a Free Cuba, 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Cuba: AFL-CIO Committee for a Free Cuba, 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Cuba: AFL-CIO Committee for a Free Cuba, 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Cuba: Florida Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Czechoslovakia, 1990-1994 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Denmark, 1980-1991 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Dominican Republic, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Dominican Republic, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Dominican Republic, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Dominican Republic, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Dominican Republic, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Dominican Republic, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Dominican Republic, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Dominican Republic, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Dominican Republic, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Dominican Republic, 1977-1990 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Ecuador, 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Egypt, 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- El Salvador, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- El Salvador, 1980-1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- El Salvador, 1980-1988 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- El Salvador, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- El Salvador, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- El Salvador, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- El Salvador, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- El Salvador, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- El Salvador, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- El Salvador, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Ethiopia, 1985-1993 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Finland, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- France, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- France, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- France, 1985-1993 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- France, 1985-1993 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Germany, 1979-1995 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Germany, 1979-1995 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Ghana, 1980-1995 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Greece, 1980-1988 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Guatemala, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Guatemala, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Guatemala, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Guatemala, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Guatemala, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Guatemala, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Guatemala, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Guatemala, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Guatemala, 1986-1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Guatemala, 1986-1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Haiti, 1974-1995 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Haiti, 1974-1995 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Haiti, 1974-1995 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Honduras, 1983-1995 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Honduras, 1983-1995 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Honduras, 1983-1995 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Hong Kong, 1986-1995 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Hong Kong, 1986-1995 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Hungary, 1989-1993 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Iceland, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- India, 1981-1994 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- India, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Indonesia, 1986-1995 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Indonesia, 1986-1995 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Ireland, 1985-1994 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Israel, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Israel, 1979-1995 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Israel, 1979-1995 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Italy, 1987-1995 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Italy, 1987-1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Jamaica, 1982-1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Jamaica, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Japan, 1981-1994 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Japan, 1982-1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Japan, 1982-1995 (Box 35, Folder 9)